ROBERT FITKIN

Software Developer

rfitkin.github.io

Cleveland, TN 37312 | C: 423-457-4446 | robertfitkin16@gmail.com

Summary

I am a software developer, specializing in app and web development. For almost three years I have been developing form applications and websites using C#, Visual Basic, SQL, HTML, and JavaScript programming languages. Although I am currently employed as a computer technician, I work with these languages everyday gaining hands on experience in all stages of software development.

Skills

- C#
- HTML
- SQL
- Visual Basic
- JavaScript
- Python
- Troubleshooting proficiency
- Windows 7 through 11

- · Excellent problem-solving skills
- Critical Thinking
- Communication
- Application installations
- Data collection and analysis
- Peer training
- Debugging
- Building trust and support

Experience

IT Computer Technician

08/2020 to Current

Life Bridges Inc.

Cleveland, TN

- Combined C# and SQL to help develop a potential new front end for an existing database.
- Developed an auction website using C#, HTML, and JavaScript for the company to sell used equipment.
- Developed a program from the ground up with C# that allows an admin to search every computer on a network for any file or file type they may be looking for from one place.
- Improved operations by working with team members and customers to find workable solutions.
- Design user friendly websites with interactive and dynamic features using .Net Framework, C#, ASP.NET, and CSS in Visual Studio
- Organized efficient daily work plans based on oral instructions and written directions to meet challenging objectives.
- Worked with team members to develop scripts to increase workplace productivity.

Help Desk Technician Lee University

08/2017 to 08/2020 Cleveland, TN

- Set up new desktop systems and configured laptops for incoming employees, loading required software and server permissions.
- Collaborated with support team to assist client stakeholders with emergent technical issues and develop effective solutions.
- Disassembled computer systems to troubleshoot and resolve hardware issues.
- Configured new employee workstations, including all hardware, software and peripheral devices.
- Consulted via telephone to understand user problems, run through testing scripts and ask questions to locate root causes.
- Maintained calm, professional demeanor when faced with high demand, high volume workloads.
- Devised incisive workarounds and resolutions for software problems.
- Explained technology-related details in easy-to-understand terms to individuals from all walks of life and in various job positions.

Education and Training

High School Diploma

Cleveland High School

Cleveland, TN

05/2015

Over 60 credits towards a Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

Lee University C

2016-2020 Cleveland, TN

References

Justin Mcmahon

Company: Intelometry Inc.

Job Title: Software Quality Assurance Analyst

Phone: (423) 331-8017

Email: Justinmcmahon66@gmail.com

Ashely Lynch

Company: Fluentstream

Job Title: Implementation Coordinator

Phone: (251) 578-0500

Email: alynch02@leeu.edu

Caleb Carroll

Company: Siskin Hospital **Job Title:** Systems Engineer

Phone: (423) 715-5518

Email: carrollcalebb@gmail.com